    Today in the process of writing the script I found the following problems 
and summary:

#!/bin/bash

SubFunction_result=PASS

if [ $SubFunction_result = PASS ]  
then
echo pass
else
echo fail
fi

# only PASS double quotes when running pass, pass on both sides double quotes,both 
sides are not overtime to get pass;
# suggested that only the middle bracket on both sides of contents and no spaces, 
line 5: [PASS: not found command, display:fail;
# Only the middle  content and no spaces, display:pass.

# ==Prepare Test File==

if [ ! -f /wlan/test_file ]; then
  echo nul > wlan/test_file
fi
if [ -f /test.txt ]; then
rm -f test.txt
fi

Note here! Have to have a space between the ! and -f, or run will prompt: look 
forward to one dimension expression.